This is the newcomer service where people from other states of Nigeria and various different countries who
attended the Sunday service for the first time came back to meet the man of God.
You unclean spirit!
Say, listen!
My body is not your temple.
I command you out!
Out!
In the name of Jesus
Come out!
In Jesus Christ name!
Congregation: Amen
You may be seated.
There are almost 7 people that have came out now.
There is a pastor among them.
And I want him to be sincere...he is on he floor now.
Why is he on the floor wearing a collar?
We are not here to make a mockery.
You are not a pastor but you call yourself a pastor.
You use evil powers.
During the time of prayer, the man of God gave a prophesy that there was man on the floor wearing a collar.
Although he called himself a pastor, he was not and was using evil power.
Let's listen to the man.
I am Pastor Victory Chiaka from
Divine Miracle Assembly in Imo State
I have a problem in my ministry.
When the ministry is growing it will grow backwards.
So, one man told me that he is the one who is troubling me. Then I ran to my friend.
My friend took me to a witch doctor.
The witch doctor told me that he would prepare a charm
for me, then I would swallow a charm he will do.
When he did the work, they would not be able to kill me.
Concerning my ministry, he promised
that those branches that failed, will never fail again.
Prophet T.B Joshua: What did you ask the witch doctor to do for you?
Man: I asked the witch doctor to do a charm for my protection.
and for the church to grow
and have a large crowd.
Man of God, please deliver me.
My name is Pastor Victory Chiaka from
Divine Miracle Assembly in Imo State
When the ministry stated to grow, all of a sudden, people began to threaten the ministry.
As they were threatening me, the church began to fold.
I went to my fellow pastor to complain about the threats;
that they said they will fold the church and kill me.
My fellow pastor said, that if I accept he would like to take me to a certain place
I said why not! So he took me to a place, to meet a herbalist doctor.
As we reached there. The witchdoctor told what to do after he performed a charm.
After that he gave me something
to put into the water.
He told me that they were going to buy
a fowl and a goat for a sacrifice.
He said that when I had brought the fowl and goat, once the sacrifice is complete, the church would start to grow.
and the people would not be able to kill me.
He also said that I would have the power to do miracles. Unlike I am suffering now.
I ran and brought the money to him and he did the sacrifice. After that he gave me a charm
that I would be in the water.
Then I went back, and put it in the water. Then I sprinkled it in church premises.
Then people started to come to the church.
If you were sick, I would give them
water to drink and in under 3 days they would recover.
As this continued happening, at a time the church started to go back again.
Then I went back to the witch doctor to advise him that the church was going back again.
Then I decided to go to another witch doctor.
As I went to another witch doctor, he said that he would help the church grow.
Then as I went there, the man performed the charm and then killed a fowl and put the tongue of the fowl
on one idol there. and mixed it with something and said that I should swallow it.
He said when I swallow it, that I would have power and that I will be protected.
He said whatever I say will happen.
So I swallowed it and I went back,
and everything that I spoke begin to happen.
The ministry begin to function very well.
I started to have a lot of branches.
At some point, the ministry to begin to slow down again.
Then I went to a third native doctor.
I told him that my church was not functioning very well.
So, he prepared and soap and told me to use it.
After that I went to my village and there they were watching Emmanuel TV.
I began watching it myself.
I returned back to my house and began to continue watching Emmanuel TV.
At a time the man of God said, "viewers all over the world, touch the screen."
So I touched the screen. As he was praying it felt like electricity shocked me.
After that, I went to take a bath that night.
I looked for the soap, but I could not find it.
Testimony Time
The soap that I received from the witch doctor disappeared.
Then in the morning, I went back to the witch doctor
and told him that I was not able to find the soap.
I asked him what made the soap disappear?
He asked me why I was watching the television when they're praying?
He asked me why should I watch that television (Emmanuel TV).
Testimony Time
When he said that it was by me watching the television
station that made the soap disappear
and come back to his shrine.
I decided that if I can watch the television and something happens to my life.
Then I have to come to down to SCOAN to see.
But the witch doctor warned me not to come.
He saw that I would come to Lagos. He said that I should not go or watch the station again.
He said that I wouldn't get any power from the SCOAN.
But I said, "but your soap disappeared!"
He said that it was forbidden to watch Emmanuel TV station.
I decided in my mind that I would be here.
When I decide to come here, one night when I was sleeping, evil spirits came to me and began to fight me.
As they fought me, they eventually left and returned back and shot me in the back.
After they shot me, I got up and my back was swelled and water began to drain from my body.
I went to many native doctors for healing,
but they were unable to heal me.
As I continued to use the soap, I saw a difference, but the sickness was still there.
When the soap disappeared, I decided that I must go to SCOAN to pray and to see if i will receive my healing.
That was the main purpose that I came that I may receive my healing, which the witch doctors weren't able
to heal. So when I came on Sunday the prayer was too hot.
It felt like a lot of things began to fall away from back.
So as I was feeling this in my back, I fell down.
It felt like I saw an angel who flashed light on me.
When I realized where I was, I was at he alter before the man of God, where I was pleading for deliverance.
I prayed that I would have the anointing of God, that I would be able to pray.
I didn't want to go back to the witch doctors.
After the prayer on Monday, I was delivered by the power of God.
When I was upstairs, the native doctor called me, and asked me where I was?
I told him that I traveled. He didn't believe me.
He said that I traveled to the place he told me not to go.
So help me man of God.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies from the SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV, changing lives, changing the nations, and changing the world.